Guide to the David Plowden Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1948-2011; Series I; 189; 41.9 linear_feet
  - July 1995 Acquisition
    - Reproducible Prints and Study Prints
      - [Locomotive] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Locomotive] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Locomotive] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Locomotive]. Scotland (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Locomotive] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Locomotive] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Locomotive] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [McNulty House]. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-321) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - [Old Oak Common] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Car] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Car] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Car] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Car] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Car] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Car]. Liverpool Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform]. Liverpool Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform]. Paddington Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform]. Waterloo Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform]. Waterloo Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Platform]. Liverpool Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Worker] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Worker] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Worker] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Worker] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Workers] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Station Workers]. Scotland (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Tracks] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Railroad Tracks]. Liverpool Station, London, England (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Train platform] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Train platform] (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - [Untitled] (865-965) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - [Untitled] (865-345) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - [Windmill] (GFB-68-3907) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - Abandoned Grain Elevators by Rock Island Railroad. Geronimo, Oklahoma (969-1542) Study print, 1969 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Carriage House, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-42) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Carriage House, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-31) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Carriage House, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-40) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Carriage House, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-219) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Carriage House. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-226) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Carriage House. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-97) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Gate House. North Easton, Massachusetts (45-2) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Ames Memorial Hall, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (864-66) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - Ames Memorial Hall, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (865-130) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - Ames Memorial Hall, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-1017) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Boston Maine Railroad Crossing Gates. Troy, New York (No number extant) Study print, 1963 (Box 98)
      - Cemetery. Danville, Vermont (STJ-571-250) Study print, 1971 May (Box 98)
      - Cemetery Fence and Gateway. Kingsville, Ohio (LFC-676) Study print, 1964 (Box 98)
      - Chair on Porch of L. B. J.'s Home. Hye, Texas (LBJ-75) Study print, 1975 (Box 98)
      - Church North of Little Falls. Little Falls, New York (NYS-1067-347) Study print, 1967 October (Box 98)
      - Church North of Little Falls. Little Falls, New York (NYS-1067-346) Study print, 1967 October (Box 98)
      - Church. Williamsville, Vermont (No number extant) Study print, 1962 October (Box 98)
      - Church. Auriesville, New York (LFC-37) Study print, 1964 (Box 98)
      - Churchyard. York, Pennsylvania (LFC-664-4) Study print, 1964 June (Box 98)
      - Columbia University Band (CU-CH-263-14) Study print, 1963 February (Box 98)
      - Cowboy. North Dakota (GP-35-7-33) Study print, 1971 (Box 98)
      - David Plowden at Cape Creek Bridge, Oregon Coast Highway. Lane County, Oregon (GFB-68-3186) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - David Plowden Developing Film, Quality Court, Portsmouth. Portsmouth, Ohio (GFB-68) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - David Plowden on Sciotoville Bridge. Sciotoville, Ohio (GFB-68-2) Study print, 1968 July (Box 98)
      - David Plowden on Sciotoville Bridge. Sciotoville, Ohio (GFB-68-2) Study print, 1968 July (Box 98)
      - David Plowden on Sciotoville Bridge. Sciotoville, Ohio (GFB-68-3) Study print, 1968 July (Box 98)
      - David Plowden. Montana (US-DP-21) Study print, 1973 (Box 98)
      - Deadwood, South Dakota (874-1847) Study print, 1974 August (Box 98)
      - Dennis Buffalo, Sr., Oglala Sioux White River Indian Reservation. South Dakota (GP-35-8-10) Study print, 1971 (Box 98)
      - Detail, Ames Carriage House. North Easton, Massachusetts (865-244) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - Detail, Ames Memorial Hall, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (865-177) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - Detail of Doorway, Library, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (865-210) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - Dickey County, North Dakota (372-116) Study print, 1972 March (Box 98)
      - Doorway, Library, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-13) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Former Post Office. Devon, Montana (No number extant) Study print, 1971 (Box 98)
      - Fort Pierre National Grasslands. South Dakota (372-496) Study print, 1972 March (Box 98)
      - Gardner's Cottage, Ames Estate, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-261) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Gardner's Cottage, Ames Estate, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-7) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Gardner's Cottage, Ames Estate, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-267) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Gardner's Cottage, Ames Estate, H. H. Richardson. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-89) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Gettysburg, Ohio (LFC-1626) Study print, 1964 (Box 98)
      - Graveyard by Tracks at Gettysburg. Gettysburg, Ohio (LFC-1625) Study print, 1964 (Box 98)
      - Grundy Co. Grain Elevator. Dike, Iowa (1083-664) Study print, 1983 October (Box 98)
      - Hat Rack, L. B. J.'s Boyhood Home. Hye, Texas (LBJ-10) Study print, 1965 (Box 98)
      - Indian Reservation. Cache Creek, British Columbia, Canada (GFB-68-4269) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - Library, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-1036) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Lyndon Johnson's Front Parlor. Hye, Texas (LBJ-8) Study print, 1965 (Box 98)
      - Mantle, Ames Memorial Hall, H. H. Richardson [Architect] and A. St. Gundens, Sculptor. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-172) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Mantle, Library, H. H. Richardson, Architect, A. St. Gundens, Sculptor. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-247) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-178) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-343) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-877) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-115) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-381) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-227) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-301) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-453) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-427) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-126) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-458) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-227) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-301) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-364) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-345) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-413) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-488) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-54) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - McNulty House. Lincoln, Massachusetts (MA-965-423) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Monon Railroad Tracks, North of Lafayette. Monon, Indiana (LFC-158) Study print, 1964 (Box 98)
      - Mt. Rushmore. Rapid City, South Dakota (874-1721) Study print, 1974 August (Box 98)
      - Mt. Rushmore. Rapid City, South Dakota (874-1724) Study print, 1974 August (Box 98)
      - Near Brookston, Indiana (LFC-485) Study print, 1985 April (Box 98)
      - New Haven Railroad Depot (since restored), H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (MA-1163-48) Study print, 1963 November (Box 98)
      - New Haven Railroad Station, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-216) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - New Haven Railroad Station, H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (865-13) Study print, 1965 August (Box 98)
      - North Dakota (372-249) Study print, 1972 March (Box 98)
      - North Dakota (GP-1152) Study print, 1971 (Box 98)
      - North Easton Depot (since restored), H. H. Richardson, Architect. North Easton, Massachusetts (HHR-965-211) Study print, 1965 September (Box 98)
      - Old Oak Common (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - Old Oak Common (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - Old Oak Common (BR-No Number) Study print, 1957 (Box 98)
      - Oliver Jensen. Johnson City, Texas (LBJ-130) Study print, 1965 (Box 98)
      - Oliver Jensen. Johnson City, Texas (LBJ-131) Study print, 1965 (Box 98)
      - Orange County, New York (No number extant) Study print, undated (Box 98)
      - Ploughed Fields. Logan County, North Dakota (GP-1770) Study print, 1971 (Box 98)
      - Pressed Tin Ceiling (Vintage), Post Office-General Store. Hye, Texas (LBJ-68) Study print, 1965 (Box 98)
      - Snow Bank. Dickey County, North Dakota (372-118) Study print, 1972 March (Box 98)
      - Steam Traction Engine. Williams Grove, Pennsylvania (WG-15) Study print, undated (Box 98)
      - Storm Clouds over Black Hills, as seen from Badlands National Monument. Black Hills, South Dakota (874-2286) Study print, 1974 August (Box 98)
      - U. VA. Serpentine Wall, Thomas Jefferson Architect. Charlottesville, Virginia (1164-1) Study print, 1964 November (Box 98)
      - Weissport, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-227) Study print, 1963 October (Box 98)
      - West Hill Cemetery. Putney, Vermont (V-764-304) Study print, 1964 July (Box 98)
      - Wheat Fields. Near Winner, South Dakota (372-487) Study print, 1972 March (Box 98)
      - Wheat Fields. North Dakota (372-2061) Study print, 1972 March (Box 98)
      - Wheat Harvest. Seneca, South Dakota (No number extant) Study print, undated (Box 98)
      - Windmill. Near Lawton, Oklahoma (GFB-68-3908) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - Windmill. Nebraska City, Nebraska (GFB-68-5986) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - Windmill. Nebraska City, Nebraska (GFB-68-5982-4) Study print, 1968 (Box 98)
      - Wounded Knee, South Dakota (GP-1206) Study print, 1971 (Box 98)
      - [Sign for the Yellow Tavern] (467-450) Study print, 1967 April (Box 99)
      - Abandoned building. Troy, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1963 (Box 99)
      - Alligator Crosshead, Close-up of the 5244. New Egypt, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1961 (Box 99)
      - Belfast, Maine (965-212) Reproducible (plus) print, 1965 September (Box 99)
      - Butler Center, Wayne County, New York (WC-910) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Canadian National Railway, 4-8-4 #6218 (Firebox and Trailing Truck Detail on Excursion Train). Saint Albans, Vermont (V-865) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 99)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, #1262 G-5 Class 4-6-2. Saint Luc, Montreal, Quebec, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway. 4-40 #136 Oldest Active Steam Train Locomotive in North America, Built 1886. New Brunswick, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, undated (Box 99)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, Armstrong Turntable Turning 4-6-2 Locomotive, Bob Hardy, Boy Helping Fireman. Greenville Junction, Maine (CPR-759) Study print, 1959 July (Box 99)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, The Glen. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (No number extant) Study print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Capt. Throop's House. Wayne County, New York (WC-1767) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Cincinnati, Ohio (1066-611) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 99)
      - Coal Silos. Wayne County, New York (WC-1485) Study print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Denver Rio Grande Western Rd. Narrow Gauge. Cumbres, Colorado (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1962 June (Box 99)
      - Engineer of a Canadian National Railway Switch Engine Type 0-8-0 Oils Around His Engine at the Engine Terminal. Hamilton, Ontario, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1959 May (Box 99)
      - Erie Canal Aqueduct. Lyons, New York (WC-1136) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Farmhouse. Near Stephentown, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1963 (Box 99)
      - Feed Mill. Clyde, Wayne County, New York (WC-2696) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Feed Mill. Wayne County, New York (WC-2400) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Fence by Erie Railroad Tracks. Lordville, New York (GFB-69-636) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 (Box 99)
      - Fire Alarm Box. Beacon, New York (NYS-463-43) Reproducible print, 1963 April (Box 99)
      - Fire Hydrant. Beacon, New York (NBF-163-136) Reproducible print, 1963 January (Box 99)
      - Fireman, Virginia Blue Ridge Railroad. Virginia (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1961 (Box 99)
      - Former Pink Elephant Saloon. Fredericksburg, Texas (LBJ-75) Reproducible (plus) print, 1965 June (Box 99)
      - Great Northern Railway 4-8-4 Steam Locomotive No. 2585, Preserved. Havre, Montana (GP-357-33) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 99)
      - Headstone. Wayne County, New York (WC-565) Study print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Hostler Cleaning Fires, Canadian Pacific Railway. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (No number extant) Study print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Hostler "Trimming" (i.e. greasing) Driving Wheels on a Reading #2124 4-8-4 locomotive. Warwick, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 August (Box 99)
      - Hostler "Trimming" (i.e. greasing) Driving Wheels on a Reading #2124 4-8-4 locomotive. Warwick, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Hostler "Trimming" (i.e. greasing) Locomotive Driving Wheels (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 99)
      - Hostler Washing Canadian Pacific Railway Steam Locomotive, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Hostler Washing Canadian Pacific Steam Locomotive. McAdam, New Brunswick, Canada (No Number Extant) Study print, 1959 August (Box 99)
      - House. Near Stephentown, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1963 (Box 99)
      - Interior, Methodist Chapel. Butler Center, Wayne County, New York (WC-1188) Study print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Jailhouse. Johnson City, Texas (LBJ-131) Study print, 1965 (Box 99)
      - John Vukovich, Deckhand, Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Lackawanna, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Hoboken, New Jersey (EL-1167-247) Reproducible (plus) print, 1967 November (Box 99)
      - Lake Ontario. West of Sodus Point, New York (WC-2883) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Lake Ontario. Wayne County, New York (WC-756) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Lamp Post. Brooklyn, New York (965-301) Reproducible (plus) print, 1965 September (Box 99)
      - Last Operating, Pennsylvania Railroad Steam Locomotive on Union Transportation Co. New Egypt, New Jersey (No number extant) Study print, undated (Box 99)
      - Lyons, New York (WC-21) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Lyons, Wayne County, New York (WC-18) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Main Street. Johnson City, Texas (LBJ-103) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 99)
      - North Dakota (GFB-68-3371) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 99)
      - Old Fire House Tower. Chatham, New York (NYS-363) Reproducible (plus) print, 1963 March (Box 99)
      - Old Fire Tower, Base of Building Florist Shop Today. Chatham, New York (NYS-363) Reproducible (plus) print, 1963 March (Box 99)
      - Ontario Northland Railway Train #147, Cochrane Connection for Train #47, Engine #700, 4-6-2. Porquis Junction, Ontario, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1953 August (Box 99)
      - Ontario Northland Railway, Train #147, Train #217. Porquis Junction, Ontario, Canada (No number extant) Study print, 1953 August (Box 99)
      - Ontario Northland Railway, Train #47, Train #147. Porquis Junction, Ontario, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1953 August (Box 99)
      - Orders, Baltimore Ohio Railroad. Harpers Ferry, West Virginia (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Palmyra, Wayne County, New York (WC) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad 2-10-0 Type. Newberry Junction, Pennsylvania (No number extant) Study print, 1954 (Box 99)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad Crossing Sign. Pennsylvania (PA-263-2) Reproducible print, 1963 February (Box 99)
      - Pennsylvania Station. New York, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1961 (Box 99)
      - Photograph Done While Student of Minor White, Trees. Near Rochester, New York (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Photograph Taken as a Student of Minor White, Exercise: Texture. Rochester, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible (plus) print, circa 1959-1960 (Box 99)
      - Photograph Taken as a Student of Minor White, Exercise: Texture. Rochester, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible (plus) print, circa 1959-1960 (Box 99)
      - Photograph Taken as a Student of Minor White, Exercise: Texture. Rochester, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Photograph taken While Student of Minor White, Exercise: Texture. Rochester, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Prairie. Near Funks Grove, Illinois (LFC-823) Reproducible print, 1964 (Box 99)
      - Putney Great Meadows. East Putney, Vermont (V-1064-51) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 99)
      - Quebec Central Railway. Near Tring Junction, Quebec, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Quebec Central Railway, Last Run of Steam Train (No number extant) Study print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Reading #2124. Warwick, New York (No number extant) Study print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Reading Company, Outer Station. Reading, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-82) Study print, 1963 October (Box 99)
      - Scene at St. John, New Brunswick in July 1959, Engine is Central Pacific Railway 5400, a 2-8-2 Bound for McAdam. Saint John, New Brunswick, Canada (No number extant) Study print, 1959 July (Box 99)
      - Sheep in Meadow, Photograph Taken as a Student of Minor White. Near Rochester, New York (No Number Extant) Study print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Smokebox, Engine #250, Hawk Mtn. Line (Bonhonomie Hattiesburg Southern Railroad 2-6-2 #250). Kempton, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-203) Reproducible (plus) print, 1963 October (Box 99)
      - Steam Locomotive Driving Sheets, Canadian National Railway 4-8-2. London, Ontario, Canada (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1953 (Box 99)
      - Sydney Louisburg Railway, Sydney Pier Engine Terminal, #103 a 2-8-2, DOSCO Steel Works in the Background (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 August (Box 99)
      - Sydney Louisburg Railway, Pier Engine Terminal, One of Two Major Engine Terminals on the System, Shown in the Background is DOSCO's Ore Stockpile. Sydney, Nova Scotia, Canada (No Number Extant) Study print, 1959 August (Box 99)
      - Telephone Pole Cross Back. Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania (PA -164-2) Reproducible print, 1964 January (Box 99)
      - "Trimming" Cranks, 4-8-4 #2124 at Warwick, New York, Reading Company, on Excursion Train, Lehigh Hudson River Railroad. Warwick, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 99)
      - Troy, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1963 (Box 99)
      - Union Transportation Co., Pennsylvania Railroad's Last Active Steam Locomotive 0-6-0 #5244. New Egypt, New Jersey (No number extant) Study print, 1961 (Box 99)
      - Unloading Mail, Baltimore Ohio #11. Piedmont, West Virginia (464-227) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 99)
      - Vinegar Vats. Wayne County, New York (WC-2550) Study print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Virginia Blue Ridge Railway #10 2-8-0, Derelict (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1961 (Box 99)
      - Walcott,Wayne County, New York (WC-885) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Washing Steam Locomotive, Canadian Pacific Railway, The Glen. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 99)
      - Waterfront. Cincinnati, Ohio (1066-1027) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 99)
      - Waterfront. Cincinnati, Ohio (1066-1024) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 99)
      - Waterfront. Cincinnati, Ohio (1066-156) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 99)
      - Wayne County, New York (WC-890) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Wayne County, New York (WC-958) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Wayne County, New York (WC-1687) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Wayne County, New York (WC-16) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Wayne County, New York (WC-860) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 99)